fullslate.com 2012-05-25

# Privacy Policy by Full Slate

Effective Date: August 6, 2008

At **Full Slate** , we respect your right to privacy and we understand that users need to control the uses of their personal information. Full Slate, Inc. (“Full Slate”, “we”, “us” or “our”) owns and operates various websites and internet-based applications that facilitate appointment scheduling, customer relationship management, marketing, promotions, and resource management (collectively, the “Services”) for service providers and their clients. This privacy policy describes our policies with respect to personal information we receive from businesses and individuals who provide services (“Service Providers”), from individuals who use the Services to schedule appointments and otherwise interact with Service Providers (“Clients”), and from visitors to our websites.

## Information Collection & Use

### Clients

You may schedule an appointment with a Service Provider whether or not you register with us. If you do not register, you will use the Services as a “guest”, in which case you will be required to enter 1) your name and 2) your email address, phone number, both or neither, as determined by the Service Provider with whom you are scheduling an appointment, and you may also be asked for other information. If you register, you will be required to enter your name, email address (which will function as your user name) and password, and will also be asked for your phone number, address, and other information. Full Slate and the Service Provider with whom you schedule an appointment use this information to send you appointment confirmations and reminders, to otherwise communicate with you about such services, and to inform you about the services in which you have expressed interest.

### Service Providers

In order to use the Services, you must first complete the registration process and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information including, but not limited to, business name, owner, address, phone number and email address. We use this information to contact you about the Services and about services in which you have expressed interest. If you or a representative of your business sends us an email or otherwise provides us an email address, we reserve the right to retain that email address. In order to market your business, we may also ask you for additional information, such as toll-free number and directory categories. We will use the foregoing information to contact you in support of delivering the Services to you, to improve or optimize the Services, and to ensure you are a valid business using the Services in accordance with the Full Slate Terms of Use. If you achieve the Payment Threshold, as defined in the Terms of Use, you will be required to enter credit card information in order to keep your account active. We will use this information solely for billing your credit card for the Services.

We will not share your schedule with anyone except as necessary for Clients to browse and schedule appointments. If you directly enter information about Clients, we will not share such information or market to such Clients unless they separately opt-in during registration.

### Surveys

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys about the Services. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to improve or optimize the Services and to provide Service Providers with aggregate information that may help them better operate their business. We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys; that company will be prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

## Communications from THE SERVICES

### Clients

We will send you appointment confirmations and reminders based on information you provide when you schedule an appointment. Further, the Service Provider with whom you schedule an appointment may contact you with any changes to, or questions about, the appointment and related services. If you choose to register with Full Slate, we will send you a welcome email to verify your user name/email address. The Service Provider with whom you schedule an appointment may occasionally send you information on their services, and we will occasionally send you information on Full Slate and other services you may find of interest. Out of respect for your privacy, we will give you the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

### Service Providers

If you choose to register with Full Slate, we will send you a welcome email to verify your user name/email address. We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to terminate your account. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. We will occasionally send you information on new services or features. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our current and/or prospective partners, including online directories and businesses that help Service Providers market their business. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

### Client Personally Identifiable Information

We will share your Personally Identifiable Information with the Service Provider with whom you schedule an appointment so the Service Provider can contact you regarding the appointment.

### Service Provider Personally Identifiable Information

We will share your information with Clients to the extent it is necessary to schedule appointments and otherwise interact with you. We use a credit card processing company to bill you for services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. We use third parties to provide directory listings and marketing services on the Services. When you sign up for these services, we will share information about your business as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties may contact you via phone or email about your business listing and to offer you additional services.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Services.

## Choice AND Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you are a Client, when you register for the Services, we will ask if you wish to receive marketing materials from Service Providers and us. If you are a Service Provider, we will ask if you wish to receive marketing materials from us. If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by emailing us at support@fullslate.com.

## Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Services, to track users’ movements around the Services and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, such as usage and volume statistics, which we use to improve and enhance the Services.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Services. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Services. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Services. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Services. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Services, but your ability to use some areas of the Services, such as surveys, will be limited. Some of our business partners may use cookies on the Services. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on the Services by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

## Links to Other Sites

The Services contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Full Slate. Please be aware that we, Full Slate, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Services and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the Services.

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire the Services, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account or by contacting us at support@fullslate.com.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number, on our payment web pages, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on the Services, you can send email us at support@fullslate.com.

## Business Transitions

In the event Full Slate goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via notice on the Services of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

We do not direct the Services to children under the age of 13. We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. As such, we will promptly delete any information and cancel any account we believe to be from children under the age of 13.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at support@fullslate.com.
